<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<Products>
	<Product>
		<ID>Tab1</ID>
		<ProductLogo>TabStripLogo.gif</ProductLogo>
		<ProductImage>TabStrip.gif</ProductImage>
		<ProductDescription>
		<![CDATA[
		<strong>t</strong>elerik r.a.d.<strong>tabstrip</strong> is a flexible component 
for building tabbed interfaces in ASP.NET applications: CSS-based text-only 
tabstrips, fully graphical with simple or overlapping image backgrounds, 
scrollable, vertical, aligned, or multi-level nested tabstrips. The product 
fully supports .NET 2.0 and the integrated Themes mechanism.<br /><br />
		r.a.d.<b>tabstrip</b> supports all major browsers Internet Explorers 4.0+, Netscape 6.0+, Mozilla 0.6+ and Opera 7+ both on PC and Mac. The product is available individually or as a part of the r.a.d.<b>controls</b> and r.a.d.<b>navigation</b> suites - "Unleashing the power of Thin Client".
		]]>
		</ProductDescription>
		<Price>$199.00</Price>
	</Product>
	<Product>
		<ID>Tab2</ID>
		<ProductLogo>PanelbarLogo.gif</ProductLogo>
		<ProductImage>Panelbar.gif</ProductImage>
		<ProductDescription>
		<![CDATA[
		<strong>t</strong>elerik 
r.a.d.<strong>panelbar</strong> is a versatile component for building 
collapsible side-menu systems and Outlook-type panels. It is developed to 
facilitate what is found in almost any web-site - the typical left/right-side 
navigation, but cannot be achieved using the conventional drop-down menu 
components.<br /><br />
		r.a.d.<b>panelbar</b> can be customized extensively (with or without CSS) to deliver attractive and convenient navigation - from standard Outlook®-bars to fully graphical side-menus. The product offers wide cross-browser compatibility (IE5+, NS7+, Mozilla, FireFox, Opera, Safari) and is available as an individual component or as part of the r.a.d.<b>controls</b> and r.a.d.<b>navigation</b> suites - "Unleashing the power of Thin Client".
		]]>
		</ProductDescription>
		<Price>$249.00</Price>
	</Product>
	<Product>
		<ID>Tab3</ID>
		<ProductLogo>MenuLogo.gif</ProductLogo>
		<ProductImage>Menu.gif</ProductImage>
		<ProductDescription>
		<![CDATA[
		r.a.d.<strong>menu</strong> is the most 
advanced drop-down menu component for ASP.NET. The product allows developers to 
build horizontal, vertical, pop-up, and scrollable menus, which mimic the 
sophistication of the Windows navigation systems. r.a.d.<strong>menu</strong> is 
shipped with an abundant set of ready-to-use skins, which can jump start your 
implementations.<br /><br />
		r.a.d.<b>menu</b> is available individually or as part of the r.a.d.<b>controls</b> and r.a.d.<b>navigation</b> suites - "Unleashing the power of Thin Client".
		]]>
		</ProductDescription>
		<Price>$249.00</Price>
	</Product>
	<Product>
		<ID>Tab4</ID>
		<ProductLogo>EditorLogo.gif</ProductLogo>
		<ProductImage>Editor.gif</ProductImage>
		<ProductDescription>
		<![CDATA[
		<strong>t</strong>elerik r.a.d.<strong>editor</strong> is the leading WYSIWYG 
rich-text editor for ASP.NET. The product can replace any TextBox with an 
intuitive Word®-like editor, which enables even non-technical users to author 
and manage HTML content as easily as writing a document. 
r.a.d.<strong>editor</strong> is available for <a 
href="http://www.sharepointcontrols.com/">Sharepoint</a>, <a 
href="http://www.mcmscontrols.com/">MCMS 2002</a> and <a 
href="http://www.telerik.com/dnn/">DotNetNuke</a>.	<br/><br/>	r.a.d.<b>editor</b> is available individually or as part of the r.a.d.<b>controls</b> suite - "Unleashing the power of Thin Client".
		]]>
		</ProductDescription>
		<Price>$349.00</Price>
	</Product>
	<Product>
		<ID>Tab5</ID>
		<ProductLogo>TreeViewLogo.gif</ProductLogo>
		<ProductImage>TreeView.gif</ProductImage>
		<ProductDescription>
		<![CDATA[
<strong>t</strong>elerik r.a.d.<strong>treeview</strong> is the supercharged 
treeview component for ASP.NET. It facilitates the display, management, and 
navigation of hierarchical data structures. The product offers many advanced 
features found in the treeview components for WinForms, but previously 
unavailable for the web.<br /><br />
		r.a.d.<b>treeview</b> features an extremely rich client and server-side API, which allows you to achieve the complex behavior found in desktop applications. Added to this is the skinning support that can nicely blend r.a.d.<b>treeview</b> into the interface of your web-site.<br /><br />
		The product is available individually or as a part of the r.a.d.<b>controls</b> and r.a.d.<b>navigation</b> suites - "Unleashing the power of Thin Client".
		]]>
		</ProductDescription>
		<Price>$249.00</Price>
	</Product>
</Products>